A Guide to the Pocahontas Mines Collection, 1883-1997
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Unscanned rolls, 1883-1997, 360 Cubic Feet; 463 boxes
  - Geological Cross-Section Showing Correlation of Lower Lee Coals [negatives] (Box 528)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Building plans for Maitland mines (Box 529)
  - USGS Survey of Kentucky River (Box 529)
  - Consolidation Coal Company, Bishop mine, map showing detail of settling ponds (Box 529)
  - Faraday Coal and Coke Company, records of drill holes in different seams (Box 529)
  - Unidentified aerial photographs (Box 530)
  - Quad map of borehole locations, Raleigh County, West Virginia (Box 530)
  - Pocahontas Coal and Coke Co., Virginia and Western Railway, West Virginia Guyandotte River Line (Box 531)
  - Maps of Raleigh and Wyoming counties, Guyandotte Mountain area (Box 532)
  - Maps showing boreholes and contour lines, same area as OSM #700502 (Box 532)
  - topographic map, Virginia, West Virginia, and Tennessee, showing Big Creek and Stony Ridge, no mine workings (Box 532)
  - Matewan Minerals Inc., map of [Breathitt?], Knott, Floyd, and Magoffin counties, Eastern Kentucky (Box 532)
  - Pocahontas incline plans (Box 533)
  - Wyoming and Raleigh counties topographic maps (Box 533)
  - Data sheets comparing New River group and Pocahontas group (Box 533)
  - Itmann Refuse Belt, Profile plan, B. K. Elliott Co. (Box 533)
  - Coal fields of the United States maps (Box 534)
  - Plan for Dry Fork layout (Box 534)
  - Maps showing coal company boundaries, no mine workings (Box 534)
  - Maps of building layouts / structure (Box 534)
  - Pocahontas Coal Co., Jenkins Jones #7, data sheets and maps of railways for mine (Box 535)
  - Matthews Mine, core hole logs datasheet (Box 535)
  - Whittaker Ridge borehole topographic map (Box 536)
  - OSM #700445, Pocahontas, Maitland Mines (Box 536)
  - Cross sections of Upper Horsepen (Box 537)
  - Raleigh County, West Virginia leases (Box 537)
  - Virginia State Highway No. 112, Crocketts Cover, Virginia, Bishop (Box 538)
  - Map showing surface features of Bishop mine (Box 538)
  - Aerial photographs (Box 539)
  - 242. Indiana-Illinois-Kentucky surface maps [negatives]; Shawneetown, Equality, Illinois (Box 539)
  - West Virginia, Amonate (Box 540)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, Department of Highways, Plan and Profile of Proposed State Highway, Tazewell County, From: .002 mi. n. int. rte. 627 (Bandy), To: 2.418 mi. n. int. rte. 627 (Bandy), 1972/06 (Box 541)
  - Consol/Pocahontas gas well lines - Turkey Gap, JenkinJones, Crozer area, south West Virginia, 1975 (Box 542)
  - Maps of Packs Knob and Sycamore surface mines (mountaintop removal); Tentative Surface Mine Proposal Map - Packs Knob, Consolidation Coal Co., Rowland Mine, Raleigh County, [196?]/03/02 (Box 542)
  - Commercial Reserves, Consol (Box 542)
  - Maps of Pine Ridge, Banjo Branch, Bishop stripping (Box 543)
  - Aerial photographs (Box 543)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Pocahontas, Virginia, Itmann mine machine drawings, building plans, and data sheets, 1958 (Box 544)
  - No. 14 Mine 4 Seam, 200-4-28 through 200-4-43, Tip Top, Anawalt, North Tazewell, Anawalt, Gary, West Virginia (Box 545)
  - No. 14 Mine 3 Seam, 200-3 thru 200-4, Gary Quad, Anawalt, Gary, West Virginia, 1973-1979 (Box 546)
  - United States Coal and Coke Co., No. 11 Side, No. 6 Mine, No. 4 Side, No. 4 & 5 Mines No. 3 Seam (Box 546)
  - 156. Beech Fork, unknown property boundaries, Houses and Roads, Amonate Colliery, map no. 4 of 4 (Box 547)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. lease line along Virginia-West Virginia border (Box 548)
  - Norfolk and Western right-of-way, Dry Fork to Cedar Bluff (Box 549)
  - No mine workings, lot map showing acreages, map states belongs to Charlie White and Pageston hardcopy (Box 550)
  - 141 House and roads, Amonate Colliery, map no. 1 (Box 551)
  - Gas wells - County map, E.W. Knight, map showing Virginia topographic and road map (Box 552)
  - No. 88, Boissevain slate dump (Box 553)
  - Flow charts for Itmann, Bishop, JenkinJones (Box 554)
  - 112. Boissevain belt line (Box 554)
  - topographic maps of southern Illinois, Equality, Ridgway, Shawneetown (Box 555)
  - Canebrake Lots 70 (Box 556)
  - Gordon and Blake Coal Co., Alvin Robertson Coal Co. No. 2 Mine, Ramsey Coal Co. (two copies) (Box 558)
  - Crane Creek No. 9 (Box 559)
  - Gary, West Virginia; Keystone, West Virginia, quad, Anawalt; Welch; No. 4 Mine, No. 4 Seam (Box 559)
  - Color coded map of Rolfe [colliery?], [circa 1910s] (Box 560)
  - Lick Branch map (Box 561)
  - New Baby Main area map (Box 562)
  - Beckwith Quad; Elkhorn Creek area maps (Box 563)
  - Howard-Winifrede, Coalburg seams (Box 564)
  - Maitland Mine Surface Layouts, PLD-1527, PLD-1528, PLD-1529 (Box 564)
  - Beckwith quad, Loop Cheek / Fayette Co., Right fork of Beards Fork (Box 565)
  - Cotiga Development Company, Freeport Outcrop (Box 566)
  - Styers Coal Co. No. 2 Mine, and unidentified maps (Box 567)
  - Winifrede No. 1-3 mines; Beckwith, West Virginia; Beards Fork, Winifrede seam (Box 568)
  - Layout of town of Pocahontas, Virginia; Pocahontas Collieries Company, Pocahontas Plant, Pocahontas, Virginia, 1906/01/10 (Box 569)
  - Pocahontas Corporation/Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. accident maps - No. 84 Colliery, 1st Cross off "G" Entry, May 25, 1948; No. 31 Colliery, "L" entry off No. 31 Mains, March 5, 1947; No. 7 Colliery, "9" right "S" entry, May 19, 1948; Angle Mine, Haulway on short ent., Albert Sells, accident, September 22, 1945; Sketch showing location of fatal accident, No. 7 Colliery, No. 5 Mine, JenkinJones, West Virginia, No. 26 Room, "S" entry, Pocahontas, Virginia, August 19, 1948; No. 22 Room, J-7 entry, sketch showing location of fatal accident, Pocahontas, Virginia, September 19, 1948, 1947-1948 (Box 569)
  - Unidentified line drawing draft (Box 569)
  - Norfolk and Western right-of-way, Wyoming County, Pinnacle and Guyandotte (Box 569)
  - Berwind, New River and Pocahontas Consolidated Coal Co., Right-of-way and Track Map, Norfolk and Western Railway, Pocahontas District, Dry Fork Branch (Box 569)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. map shows tracks, creek, buildings, roads located Upland, West Virginia (Box 569)
  - Consol Coal Co., Carswell Hollow, Maitland, King Coal building (Box 569)
  - Profile Belt and Stockpile Area, Dry Fork (Box 569)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., recoverable reserves, 1965/01/01 (Box 570)
  - Welch Quadrangle No. 24, USGS 1971 map, and topographic map of Adkin, Bottom Creek, Shawnee [Mountain?] (Box 570)
  - Map shows tracings of Maitland seams #3 and 4 (Box 570)
  - topographic map, Wyoming and McDowell counties, West Virginia, topographic quadrangle (Box 570)
  - Amonate No. 31 Hollow, Plan View, Ponds (Box 570)
  - Haul road profile C&R and Brenkee (Box 571)
  - topographic maps, Amonate quad, no mine workings (Box 571)
  - Maitland map (Box 571)
  - Laeger, Welch, Bramwell quadrangles, Richlands, Virginia, Pounding Mill, Virginia-West Virginia maps (Box 571)
  - Pageton Land Co., Keystone, West Virginia, 4/25/1958; Pageton lots and houses, 1958/04/25 (Box 572)
  - Plan views, Pre-existing ponds, Nos. 1-7, 31 Hollow, 1981/08/28 (Box 572)
  - Plan for unknown location with coal bin, bath house, parking lot, pump house, roads, and tracks (Box 572)
  - Tennessee topographic maps, Eagan quadrangle / Mingo Mountain quadrangle and areas south (Box 572)
  - JenkinJones plans and drawings for belts, storage pile, etc. (Box 572)
  - 2 maps of unidentified location, Nos. 8 & 9, Section A-A (Box 572)
  - Plans for Amonate Shop at Amonate, Virginia, 1943 (Box 573)
  - Lee Dye Bishop, Virginia, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. reports and maps, 1952/12/31 (Box 573)
  - Cross Section and pond plans at Bishop (Box 573)
  - Girl Scout Camp, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Bland County Lands (Box 573)
  - Datasheets, Amonate cross sections of disturbed lands (Box 573)
  - Supply and shop building for Colliery #31, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Amonate, West Virginia (Box 573)
  - Chilton Seam, Rowland Mines, Beckley, West Virginia, Consol, Southern Appalachian Exploration (Box 574)
  - Map showing Amonate Mine area, West Virginia/Virginia, no mine workings (Box 574)
  - Profile Dry Fork & Belt from Dry Fork Mine to Bin, no mine workings (Box 574)
  - Itmann Refuse Piles, cross-sections of abandonment plan figure no. 6, no mine workings (Box 574)
  - Old Tipple Photographs, pictures of buildings near a mine (Box 574)
  - Greasy Creek Shaft, Bishop Refuse Disposal -Facility-Dalton Branch, Regrade Profile and Mine Opening for McGlothlin Coal Co. (Box 574)
  - Small grid drawing of unidentified location (Box 574)
  - Norfolk Mines, Portion of 8-#13-1-L. entry, showing George Wade accident case, 1908/08/11 (Box 575)
  - Right of way and track maps, Norfolk & Western Railway, Pocahontas District, Virginia and Bishop, West Virginia, 1931/12/31 (Box 575)
  - Lillybrook Coal Co. wire crossing plans, 1936, 1949 (Box 575)
  - No. 31 mine, unidentified location (Box 575)
  - Berwind No. 1 Tipple Photo (Box 575)
  - Accident drawing, No. 3 Entry (Box 575)
  - Map of Laurel Fork of Bluestone River (Box 575)
  - Ponds Below Amonate Preparation Plant (Box 575)
  - X-section up Dalton Branch, Bishop, 1972/05/24; Norfolk & Western Railway Co., 1939/08/01, 1939/08/01, 1972/05/24 (Box 576)
  - Proposed chute, No. 4 Seam, Jenkin Jones, Ballard Harmon BR; Location of Tracks in No. 8 Hollow; and related drawings (Box 576)
  - Surface contours, Matthews mine area (Box 576)
  - Maitland - ponds, drainpipe, etc., no mine workings (Box 576)
  - Escape hoist - Consol Maitland mine, building plans (Box 576)
  - (Stephenson) Buckeye Tipple Tracings (Box 577)
  - Property maps, Johnson County, Kentucky (Box 577)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Amonate, Virginia, shop bath house, 1949/06/27 (Box 578)
  - Newhall subdivision made by New River and Pocahontas Consolidated Coal Co. situated in Big Creek District, McDowell County, West Virginia, 1954/08/31 (Box 578)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., cross sections of Peerless refuse, 1970/10/13 (Box 578)
  - topographic map, McDowell and Tazewell counties, Virginia and West Virginia (Box 578)
  - Property lines, unknown location (Box 578)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Maitland mine, building plans (Box 578)
  - Ponds on Grassy Spur (Box 578)
  - Contour/topographic maps showing Three Forks area, seam locations (Box 579)
  - Pocahontas Mining Corporation, Berwind Leasehold, Amonate (Box 579)
  - Property maps, McDowell and Mercer counties (Box 579)
  - Lease and property maps in West Virginia (Box 579)
  - Turkey Gap maps, ca. 1970s (Box 580)
  - Cross section showing Pocahontas coal seams (Box 580)
  - Contour map, Tazewell and McDowell counties (Box 580)
  - topographic map of the southern United States (Box 580)
  - Amonate prospecting data (Box 580)
  - Analysis of coal from Webster County, West Virginia (Box 580)
  - Insurance maps, Wenonah Colliery (Box 580)
  - Kmains survey data (Box 580)
  - Map showing tipple, tracks, and parking facility - next to Elkhorn Creek (Box 580)
  - Unidentified map (Box 580)
  - OSM #700807 Data (Box 580)
  - Track Layout, Berwind No. 1 Tipple, No. 2 and No. 5 Yard, 1957 (Box 581)
  - Tazewell County, Virginia, showing - primary and secondary highways (Box 581)
  - Peerless Coal and Coke Company, topographic and general surface around King Slope (Box 581)
  - Property line - unknown location (Box 581)
  - Map showing Guyandotte property (Box 581)
  - Maitland refuse sediment pond and haul road access road (Box 581)
  - Consol Coal Co., Crane Creek No. 11, Belt drive (Box 581)
  - Lease and property map along Pinnacle Creek (Box 581)
  - topographic maps of Matthews Mine area, contour lines and surface features, 1978/06/15 (Box 584)
  - Contour map for Virginia, Consolidation Coal Co., 1979 (Box 586)
  - Chart, Estimated Recoverable Reserves Remaining in the Pocahontas Low Volatile Coking Coal Field as of December 31, 1957, 1957/12/31 (Box 586)
  - Hand drawings, Cranes Cliff area, East Mine Crop, Pocahontas Land Corporation, 1959/01/01 (Box 586)
    Includes CON1709
  - Contour maps for unidentified locations and scanned map CON1708 (Caswell Creek No. 6 Seam) (Box 586)
  - Vertical scales for Proposed Lease No. 1, Beckley and Sewell Seam Sections, W.M. Ritter Lumber Co., Columbus, Ohio, 1948/12/01 (Box 587)
  - OSM #700032.08 Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., East Mine Crop, Tazewell Co., Virginia, Mercer Co., West Virginia, Survey, 1951/07 (Box 587)
  - Faraday Coal and Coke Company, Property Map, Pocahontas Coal Lands, Tazewell Co., Virginia, and McDowell Co., West Virginia (Box 587)
    Color coded, similar to CON2501.
  - Vertical scales for Beckley and Sewell Seams, W.M. Ritter Lumber Co. (Box 587)
  - Drainage and location maps, including Consolidation Coal Co., Pageton Preparation Plant; C and R Coal Co.; Consolidation Coal Co., Beech Fork Mine; Jo Flo Coal Co., Bishop, Virginia (Box 587)
  - Property maps and leaseholds, Lillybrook Coal Co. and Fire Creek Smokeless Fuel Co. (Box 588)
  - topographic map of Raleigh Co., West Virginia (Box 588)
  - West Virginia Coal mines served by The Virginian Railway, lease and property map (Box 589)
  - Contours and Borehole locations of D. Holes #172-155, unidentified location (Box 589)
  - Map of McDowell Co., West Virginia, and Tazewell Co., Virginia, featuring Little and Big Stone Ridge, Jacob's Fork, Amonate, Canebrake, etc. (Box 589)
  - USGS maps, West Virginia, Virginia, Kentucky, Tennessee, North Carolina, ca. 1970s (Box 591)
  - OSM #700148, Properties and mine workings, Brookside, KY, B.W. Whitfield, Jr. and Bell Coal Co., 1948/01/01 (Box 592)
    See also CON149, CON1141-CON1142.
  - Electric facilities in the United States (Box 592)
  - topographic map, Wyoming and McDowell counties, West Virginia, 1915 (Box 593)
  - OSM #700152, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Norfolk, No. 3 Seam, 1957/01/01 (Box 595)
    See also CON153.
  - OSM #700139, Itmann Mine, Itmann, Guyandotte, and Still Run leases (3 maps) (Box 595)
    Includes CON1102 and CON1103
  - OSM #700139, Nine maps, Sewell Seam, Itmann No. 6 Seam, unidentified contour maps, 1954/01/01, undated (Box 596)
    Includes CON1224_1, CON1224_2, and CON1225
  - 3 topographic/contour maps for Stoney Ridge area, McDowell Co., West Virginia, Tazewell Co., Virginia, and Tennessee borders (Box 602)
  - OSM #700127, Maps marked D-1 through D-16 (Box 604)
    Includes CON2674
  - OSM #700142, Crozer Coal and Land Company (4 maps) (Box 606)
    Includes CON1077-1079
  - OSM #700316, strip mines in Flattop region, McDowell, Mercer, and Wyoming Co. (4 maps) (Box 608)
    Includes CON1114-1116
  - Structural Geologic Map of Bell County, Kentucky (Box 610)
  - Unidentified elevation map (Box 611)
  - Upheaval Mining Near Amonate (Box 611)
  - Amonate No. 3 Seam (Box 611)
  - No Name Grid-Contour [unidentified location] (Box 611)
  - Berwind Map (Box 612)
  - Bransford North Half (Box 612)
  - Grid covering Saline and Gallatin counties, Illinois (Box 612)
  - The Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., photo map of Itmann and Guyandotte Leaseholds (Box 612)
  - Photo of Parcel Nos. I-R3, I-R4, I-R5, I-R6 (Box 612)
  - Parcel plots near Little Neck Bay, including Long Island Railroad Co., 2/13/1956, and unknown land tract map, 1956/02/13 (Box 613)
  - Lillybrook map (Box 613)
  - Tract along Tug River and Elkhorn Creek (Box 613)
  - Map of Unidentified mine with room and pillar entries and surface contour augering (Box 613)
  - Beards Fork Eagle, possibly Fayette County, West Virginia (Box 614)
  - Map of J.B.B. Coal Co. (Box 614)
  - PLD-1474, 4 maps: Conner Coal Co.; Howard Colliery, Chattaroy, West Virginia; Winifrede Outcrop and Taylor Seam; and unidentified locations (Box 614)
  - OSM #700715, Laxton Mine (Box 614)
  - Map of J.B. and B. Colliery Co. No 13 and No. 4 Mines and Maher C. and C. Co. No. 2 and 3 Mines, scale 1":100', 1906/05/10 (Box 615)
    Has two orange stickers marking benchmark grid coordinates.
  - Nassau Coal Co., No. 11 Mine, No. 3 Seam, Blackwolf West Virginia, Posted To- 09/25/1950 (Box 615)
  - No. 33G, Unidentified Mine (Box 615)
  - Unfinished Mine Map, possibly B&B No. 3 Mine or Foster No. 6 Mine (Box 615)
  - Flournoy Colliery Co. No 3 and No 1 Mines, McDowell County, Scale 1":100' (Box 616)
    Marytown, West Virginia shown on map.
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Lick Branch and Maybeury property map with parcels laid out and acreage tabulations (Box 616)
  - Maybeury Land Company. Map of Land Parcels and US. Highway 52, Mercer and McDowell counties West Virginia (Box 616)
  - PLD-1485.02, Map section of unidentified mine with colored production timing panels. (Box 616)
  - Hurricane Brch. No. 5, (Bill Allison) (Box 616)
  - PLD-1485.01 Norfolk No. 3 Angle Colliery (Box 616)
  - Map section of unidentified contour mine (Box 617)
  - OSM #700762, Shawnee, Peerless, and Bottom Creek Mines Map. 19 (Box 617)
  - No. 14 Mine, PLD-1623, No. 4 seam, Road Fork, sec 2. S33,000 to 38,000 E9000 to 28,000 (Box 617)
  - TWIN BR. MINE, Pocahontas No. 6 seam or Davy seam (Box 617)
  - PLD-1607, No. 1 Map, No. 3 Seam. Mines No. 4 & 10, East End, 1-3 (Box 618)
  - PLD-1516, Maitland No. 4 seam, new Four Mains and North diagonals. (Box 618)
  - PLD-1471.03, John Cooper & Cos Stirling Colliery, Mercer county West Virginia. (Box 618)
  - Beards Fork Mine, No. 2 Gas Seam. (Box 618)
  - PLD-1469.01 and PLD-1469.02, Roanoke Coke and Coal No. Seam Workings (Box 619)
  - PLD-1468.01 Arlington. Mine map with colorized production timing panel and depicts town of Keystone West Virginia. (Box 619)
  - Maitland No. 4 New 2nd right section entries into No. 4 Seam (Box 619)
  - No. 10 Mine, 1-3 East, PLD-1603 (Box 619)
  - PLD-1486.01, Consolidated Collieries Company, Louisville & Goodwill, Switchback West Virginia (Box 619)
  - PLD-1486.02, Consolidated Collieries Company, Baby Mine (Box 619)
  - OSM #700759, Mill Creek Coal Co. Pocahontas Coal and Coke Co. Pocahontas Property Map (Box 620)
    Depicts property, water, and timber rights and leases of Pocahontas Coal & Coke Co. to Various operators on West Virginia/Virginia Border.
  - OSM #700821, Rolf No. 3 Seam, 102 (Box 620)
  - OSM #700403, Louisville & Goodwill Collieries, Goodwill Mine, No. 3 Seam. (Box 620)
  - Messrs. WM. Booth & Co., Reliance Colliery, PLD-1499 Booth-Bowen, Mercer County West Virginia. (Box 620)
  - OSM #700855, Bluff Branch and Bluff Mountain, Stanley Coal Company No. 1 Mine. (Box 620)
  - OSM #700744, Peerless No. 4 Seam (Box 621)
  - OSM #700849 Lick Branch Mine, No. 3 Seam. (Box 621)
  - OSM #700837 Killarney Mine, Sheet Nos. 3, 4, and 5, main headings, 34 right, 35-36, and 37 right (Box 621)
  - OSM #700822 Sagamore No. 2 mine. No. 3 seam. (Box 621)
  - OSM #700721, Itmann No. 4 Mine, 1956/02/14 (Box 622)
  - OSM #700791 Crozer Elkhorn Lease, No. 3 Seam. (Box 622)
  - OSM #700775, Battleship Mine No. 3 (Box 622)
  - OSM #700856, Angle Mine, No. 3 Seam (Box 622)
  - OSM #700719, Pinnacle No. 1 Mine, Pinnacle Coal and Coke Co. McComas and Mercer Counties, West Virginia, by T.O. Deaumer Eng., 1906/06 (Box 623)
  - OSM #700789, East Mine, mine closure map, Mercer County West Virginia/Tazewell County Virginia. (Box 623)
    Shows extent of mining in closing days of operations at mine.
  - OSM #700833, Pinnacle No. 6 Mine, No. 6 seam - C. Creek (Box 623)
  - OSM #700813, Itmann No. 3 Mine, Started 4/13/60 (Box 623)
  - OSM #700846, Crane Creek No. 3 Mine, Lease No. 9. (Box 623)
  - PLD-1422, Mine Map of South Side Mine No. 2. Loup Creek Colliery Co. Beards Fork, West Virginia, 1921/06/15 (Box 624)
  - PLD-1424, Beards Fork Mine No. 2 gas seam (Box 624)
  - No. 2 Mine No. 4 Seam. Map No. 1/2-4W (Box 624)
  - PLD- 1620, 14-11-13, No. 14 Mine-No. 3 Seam (Box 624)
  - PLD- 1487, Norfolk C & C Co. No. 1 Mine (Box 624)
  - PLD-1503, Gary No. 1 Map (4 sections) (Box 625)
  - PLD-1601, 2-3, No. 1 and 10 Mines No. 3 seam (Box 625)
  - PLD-1526, Maitland No. 4 Seam. Carswell Mains, 1st Right, King Slope. (Box 625)
  - PLD-1526, Carswell Mine No. 3. No. 3 and 4 seams. (Box 625)
  - PLD-1517, Maitland Mine, Northwest Mains, No. 4 Seam (Box 626)
  - 3-4, No. 2 and 4 Mine (Box 626)
  - PLD-1635, PC & C Co., Faraday C&C Co. Property and topographic Map of unknown location. (Box 626)
  - PLD- 1621, 12-3 No. 3 Seam. South End. 14-12-3. (Box 626)
  - Eagle No.7- 4 Mines (Box 626)
  - 64, Map of No. 6 an 8 mines (Box 627)
  - Map of Bransford, Illinois Property (Box 627)
  - PLD-1503.033, Map of No. 9 and No. 14 mines and surrounding property parcels. (Box 627)
  - Map of No. 2 and No. 1 Mines around Gary, West Virginia. (Box 627)
  - Bottom Creek from "A" to "B", Transferred from Map No. 2604 (Box 627)
  - PLD- 1503.041, Pocahontas Corporation Property Map. McDowell County, West Virginia. Tazewell County Virginia (Box 627)
  - Map of No. 5 Mine. Started 1969/08 (Box 627)
  - Beards Fork Mine, Big Eagle Lick Branch, Punch Mines and Strip (Box 628)
  - Beards Fork Eagle Mine, Hard copy No. 2 (Box 628)
  - Peerless C&C Co. Dip Section #2 Mine, No. 3 Seam (Box 628)
  - Mine No. 5 Upper Half (Box 628)
  - Map of Mines of the Hensley Coal Company, McDowell West Virginia. (Box 628)
  - OSM #700731, Goodwill No. 1. Map, No. 1 sublease, No. 6 Seam (Box 629)
  - Peerless Seam Stripping (Box 629)
  - Map of Big Eagle Stripping, Beards Fork mine (Box 629)
  - Map of Beards Fork Punch Mines/Little Eagle Punch Mines (Box 629)
  - OSM #700738 Crane Creek No. 6 Seam (Box 629)
  - OSM #700810, No. 4 North Mine, Sullivan (Box 629)
  - OSM #700708. No. 11 Mine, US Coal and Coke Company, blueprint (Box 630)
  - Evaluation Of Deep Mining of Pocahontas No. 9 Seam. (Box 630)
    Large USGS map with coal reserve estimation shown.
  - OSM #700740, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc.- Southern Division of Consolidation Coal Company, Maitland Mine No. 4 seam (Box 630)
    Map shows placement of equipment power cables, conveyor belts, the mine Fan and air shafts. Most likely used by mine electricians and shift foremen.
  - OSM #700676 Olga No.2 Mine, Olga Coal Company. (Box 630)
  - Map showing coal company lease parcel boundaries along No. 3 seam outcrop and along Elkhorn Creek. (Box 630)
  - PLD-1631, No.6 Mine, No. 3 Seam, Map No. 6-3, 1959/05/15 (Box 631)
    Map of contour mining showing geological cross-sections of coal outcrops.
  - PLD-1627, 1-4w, No. 2 Mine (Box 631)
  - PLD-1622, No. 14 Mine, Freeman Branch & Martha Dillion Branch south mains, No. 4 seam, section 1-4-5 (Box 631)
  - Weyanoke - Upper Section, Mercer County School Lands Map. (Box 631)
  - PLD-1615 Blue Mountain Mining Company Inc. No. 1 Mine. Pocahontas Land Corp- owner, U.S. Steel Corp - Lessee. Hawley Coal Mining Corp - Sublessee. No. 6 & 9 Mines No. 3 Seam, 1960/09/08 (Box 632)
    Large roll is 95% blank.
  - PLD-1604, No. 10&11 Mines No. Three Seam (Box 632)
  - PLD-1470 Mill Creek C & C Co. East Mine (Box 632)
  - PLD-1632. No. 9 Mine East. No. 4 Seam 7-4 (Box 632)
  - OSM #700746. Thomas Lease, Thomas mains. Map panel 1-A (Box 632)
  - PLD-1616. No. 6 Mine, No.3 Seam, Map No. 7-3, 1963/03/28 (Box 633)
  - PLD-1472. Elkhorn Mine No. 3 seam. (Box 633)
  - PLD-1594. No.5 & 11 Mines United States Map No. 4 - No. 3 Seam (Box 633)
  - PLD- 1484, Louisville, Booth-Bowen Coal and Coke Co. No. 1, 2, & 3 Drift mines (Box 633)
  - Property Map of Page Coal and Coke Company (Box 633)
  - PLD-1626, No. 14 Mine, No. 5 seam (Box 633)
  - Map of the Fordson Coal Company Inc., Mines No. 1 and 5, No.5 Lower Half, 1921/18/08 (Box 634)
  - PLD-1612. No. 9 mine. No.4 Seam. Sec 1-A (Box 634)
  - PLD-1490. Louisville. No. 1, 2, and 3. Mines (Box 634)
  - PLD-1595. No. 1&2 mines. Hood Mine. US4-2 (Box 634)
  - PLD-1988, Weyanoke C & C Co. property map (Box 634)
  - PLD-1625. No 14 Mine - No. 4 seam. map section No. 3 (Box 635)
  - PLD-1628 No. 2 mine 4-4W (Box 635)